Vamshidhar Telugu

Kurnool, 518002 | 8106483285 teluguvamshi77@gmail.com

Mobile Application Developer with **2 years** of experience in developing applications for a Fintech Startup. Hands on experience in developing mobile apps using **Flutter** and web apps using **ReactJs**. Experienced in using version management software like **Git**. Excellent track record of soft skills including leadership, collaboration & communication.

EXPERIENCE

Android App Developer

Apr 2021 - Present

ZeroPay Pvt Ltd, Bangalore (Remote)

- Developed a mobile app that now has **100k+ downloads** on playstore.
- Lead the Mobile Front-End team
- Used MVCS architectural pattern.
- The app is developed using **Flutter** framework (An opensource framework by Google to develop cross-platform applications)

Android App Developer Intern

Mar 2021 - Apr 2021

Vendorskart Online Services Pvt Ltd, New Delhi (Remote)

- Developed a mobile application for their warranty portal.
- Used **Git & GitHub** to manage the project.
- Learn't how to work in a Team setting.

Projects

ZeroPay - Flutter Mobile App

- Flutter, Dart, MVCS Architecture, REST API Integration
- 100K+ Downloads on Playstore

Admin Console – ReactJS Webapp

• ReactJs, Redux Toolkit, Antd UI, AWS Lambda

Feather - Flutter Mobile App

- Flutter, Dart
- 10K+ Downloads with an average rating of 4.0 (As of 15/04/2022)

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.) - ECE

Jul 2019 - Jun 2023 (Expected)

Sree Vidyanikethan Engineering College, Tirupati

SKILLS

Flutter, ReactJs, AWS Lambda, Python, Git & GitHub, Java, OOP, Javascript, Typescript, Html & Css, MongoDB, SQL

LICENSES & CERTIFICATIONS

AWS Academy Graduate - AWS Academy Cloud Foundations	2022
Amazon Web Services Training and Certification - https://bit.ly/30eDuAC	

Pearson MePro Level 10

2019

Pearson - https://bit.ly/3jG2pix

5 Star Rated Python Problem Solver

2019

HackerRank - https://www.hackerrank.com/ece_19121a04m2